I know, I know, what you must do is train.
Ya sé, ya sé, la que te queda es entrenar.
The thing about gymnastics is that you release endorphins, do you understand?
Lo que tiene la gimnasia es que uno libera endorfina, ¿me entendés?
And that helps with stress relief, depression, among other things.
Y eso es... te saca el estrés, te saca la depresión.
I mean, gymnastics really help out in so many ways.
O sea, la gimnasia ayuda en un montón de cosas.
The thing is, when someone doesn't have the physical... attitude,
El tema es cuando uno no tiene la actitud... física,
when one doesn't have the willpower.
cuando uno no tiene la voluntad.
Tell me where I can find it because if there's somewhere selling me
Decirme dónde voy a buscarla, porque si hay en un lugar que a mí me vendan
willpower or the right attitude towards training, going to the gym.
la voluntad o la actitud para hacer gimnasia, para ir y entrenar.
Oh my God, please tell me where it is because I just don't have it.
Y que hay Dios mío, por favor, decime a dónde, porque yo no la tengo.
I don't have it, I can't seem to find it, it's nowhere inside me.
No la tengo, no la encuentro, no está dentro de mí.
Wherever the hell I left it, assuming it exists since everyone says,
No sé dónde mierda la tengo, si es que está que todos te dicen,
You start off...
Vos empezás...
Once you get started with the gym, you always feel like doing more.
Y una vez que empezás a hacer gimnasia, cada vez querés hacer más.
It never happened to me before!
No me pasó en la puta vida!
I hate it! I go to the gym, work out, and come back swearing. Do you understand me?
La sufro! Voy al gimnasio, hago gimnasia y vengo puteando. ¿Me entendés?
Because sometimes, I just don't feel like going.
Porque el otro día... no se me canta un huevo ir.
All I want to do is sit at home; I don't feel like working out.
Tengo ganas de sentarme en mi casa, no tengo ganas de hacer gimnasia.
What am I supposed to do, sister?
¿Qué voy a hacer, boluda?